There's this concept that
I and we developed
at Fandroid early on
called walking up the
then down the What
this means is that
most founders they're go
for the biggest names
VCs first They go
for like the hottest
names they go for
like people who have
like good signal right
But those people are
at the top of
the We encourage founders
to walk up the
first So you go
for other folks who
are like maybe there's
like a new VC
in and then they
just raised like a
small pocket of but
they're they're ready to
Like get some of
these newer names first
Maybe there certain angels
whatever like in multiple
rounds you can still
get angels involved Angels
like I customers or
something So you kind
of stack up And
some of these they
could even be like
we've gotten a of
Taiwanese capital into Southeast
Asian startups recently Like
we've always had a
great relationship with Taiwan
and VCs And so
maybe you get some
of the who are
like say not the
usual suspects Now if
you start stacking up
let's say you're raising
2 million right And
you got like one
and million dollars from
all kinds of then
you go to the
name that you want
And you say hey
Studio 65 VC I
have half my round
of my 3 million
closed You want to
get in or not
Yeah you know and
we're closing out the
rest of the half
pretty soon but somebody
recommended I speak to
you right My friend
who is your profile
company environment I to
you but we don't
have too much time